[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The letters , six in all , were sent within two hours of each other and represented dozens of power generators .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"represented\", does the state of the participant \"dozens\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I expected to pay for this service , but imagine my surprise when I received a bill for MORE than what I paid to have the original return prepared .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the state of the participant \"what\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"All you can do is take each section ( individual video ) and edit them together on software .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"edit\", does the state of the participant \"them\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had a great stay , your service was excellent and we will use you again !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the state of the participant \"We\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They offer an exceptional compensation package including a healthy salary , comprehensive benefits program , and ample room for associates to grow within the firm .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grow\", does the state of the participant \"associates\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Your suggestion to introduce the concept discussed with one of the Lays is welcomed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"introduce\", does the state of the participant \"concept\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Like William Shakspere RAPHAEL ( the painter ) died on his April birthday Laura & Bridget 's day :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the state of the participant \"RAPHAEL\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Yahoo! Mail has the best spam protection around\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the state of the participant \"protection\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i know you remember the bet .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You need either a filter for each device except the DSL modem , or a whole home filter which filters all the jacks , except the one which the DSL modem connects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filters\", does the state of the participant \"filter\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"She said a shower would be grand .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"She\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The price of crude oil on the international market hit a record $ 70.85 a barrel due to the vulnerability of oil and gas fields in the Gulf of Mexico .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hit\", does the state of the participant \"$\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A Yellowstone wolf was found dead , hit by a car , on a Colorado highway last year , several hundred miles from home .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the state of the participant \"wolf\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Joe removed a wasp nest for our condominium building and we appreciated the environmentally friendly method and prompt , friendly and informative service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the state of the participant \"Joe\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Andreas Bechtolsheim built a microcomputer ; Vinod Khosla recruited him and Scott McNealy to manufacture computers based on it , and Bill Joy to develop a UNIX - based OS for the computer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the state of the participant \"microcomputer\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I work for a large retail company recently expanding our operations into Canada and had to travel to ensure all of our computer network equipment was installed properly and on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"work\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Americans detected the attempt to infiltrate the urban areas and were already redeploying troops from the rural areas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"infiltrate\", does the state of the participant \"areas\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The intruders slit the screen of the window .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"slit\", does the state of the participant \"screen\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Pools The Mariner of the Seas and Liberty both had salt water pools - which most cruise ships have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the state of the participant \"pools\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I believe he must have waited among the gorse bushes through which the path winds and struck him down as he passed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"struck\", does the state of the participant \"him\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There 's plenty of parking , and I 've never had an issue with audience members who wo n't stop talking or answering their cellphones .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stop\", does the state of the participant \"members\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"One thought is to have just the agenda as a couple topics and then lead in with the first two questions as I 've listed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"listed\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I understand how competitive the process has become , but I felt that with my work experiences , recommendations , personality , extracurricular activities , etc. that this would compensate for my disability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"become\", does the state of the participant \"process\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rigged\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We need for interviewers to commit either to the morning ( 9 am - 12 pm ) or afternoon ( 2 pm - 5 pm ) complete session .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commit\", does the state of the participant \"interviewers\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We took our beloved kitty to him and it came back dead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the state of the participant \"kitty\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Hundreds of people are feared dead in Mississippi , and the Louisiana city of New Orleans is badly flooded .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"flooded\", does the state of the participant \"city\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had a great stay , your service was excellent and we will use you again !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the state of the participant \"We\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In Texas , BP shut its 460,000 barrels per day refinery and Marathon shut its 72,000 bpd plant .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shut\", does the state of the participant \"plant\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I need something reliable and good looking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the state of the participant \"something\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"By comparison , outdoor cats have a life expectancy of 3 - 7 years depending on how many predators are in the local environment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"cats\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I dropped the truck off in the morning and it was ready that afternoon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dropped\", does the state of the participant \"truck\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" There have no business being there unless they are undermining Pakistan , '' says a Pakistani official .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the state of the participant \"official\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Iran is encircled by Afghanistan , by the Gulf States , Iraq and the Moslem republics of the former Soviet Union .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"encircled\", does the state of the participant \"Iran\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"( Participants pledged to raise at least $ 100,000 by bundling together cheques of up to $ 1,000 from friends and family .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raise\", does the state of the participant \"$\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Cullen and Dykman ( attorneys for Boston Gas Company ) approved all of our changes on the agreement to release the Tenn and Iroq space back to Boston Gas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"release\", does the state of the participant \"space\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"By comparison , outdoor cats have a life expectancy of 3 - 7 years depending on how many predators are in the local environment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"cats\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"You have two screws that attach the sight to the wang .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"You\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The rapid victory during the first Gulf War cemented this perception .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cemented\", does the state of the participant \"perception\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We need responses or direction by no later than COB on Monday , October 30 , 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the state of the participant \"We\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i know you remember the bet .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Arial photos , loose connections to AQ Kahn and Libya make up the evidence that the group presented .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"presented\", does the state of the participant \"evidence\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They said that we were to be charged for this room regardless because we did not cancel within the 72 hours .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"They\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I remain convinced that if we can just get the facts in front of people they will modulate their approach .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"modulate\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Xinhua reports that a wide range of Iraqi political forces on Tuesday condemned Sharon 's murder of Sheikh Ahmed Yassin , a religious leader of Hamas , the day before .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemned\", does the state of the participant \"murder\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Arial photos , loose connections to AQ Kahn and Libya make up the evidence that the group presented .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"presented\", does the state of the participant \"group\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"At one point they told me the dog had been fixed , the next day it had n't .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the state of the participant \"dog\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Previous reviewers said they were pushy and I can understand that , but I find the staff more helpful than anything else .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"understand\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A girl raises her hand .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raises\", does the state of the participant \"hand\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Attached are the draft Schedule to the ISDA Master Agreement , together with Paragraph 13 to the ISDA Credit Support Annex .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the state of the participant \"Schedule\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They have unbeatable price in town and deliver on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"They\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dr. Mann killed our pet\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the state of the participant \"pet\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We had fewer social benefits at that time for people so many immigrants were not counted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"counted\", does the state of the participant \"immigrants\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The good news is that all of this is temporary , because the evolution of international law has always adapted itself to reality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adapted\", does the state of the participant \"itself\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"involving\", does the state of the participant \"children\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I called and asked about the price for hair updo and the receptionist or owner who aswered the phone refused to tell me , or even just give me an approximate price range .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"aswered\", does the state of the participant \"phone\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In other words the table is set .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"set\", does the state of the participant \"table\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"you play too much cod ;P\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the state of the participant \"you\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I called them for an estimate and they INSULTED ME WHEN I ASK THEM QUESTIONS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"INSULTED\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"James Bateman came the day I called and fixed the problem quickly and efficiently .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the state of the participant \"problem\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I left you a voice mail on Friday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the state of the participant \"mail\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There is a very good book on the subject that was written by General Vo Nguyen Giap .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"written\", does the state of the participant \"book\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the state of the participant \"laptop\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Senate increases NASA funding\"\nQuestion: In the event \"increases\", does the state of the participant \"funding\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The US lost yet another helicopter to hostile fire near Habbaniyah in the Sunni heartland , but this time the crew was safe .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the state of the participant \"US\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I sent a graphic that would have been distorted if printed as it was .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"distorted\", does the state of the participant \"graphic\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called them for an estimate and they INSULTED ME WHEN I ASK THEM QUESTIONS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"INSULTED\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"confessed\", does the state of the participant \"Bernard\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The Agel compensation plan includes the principles that ensure that promise can be fulfilled for those who work at it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fulfilled\", does the state of the participant \"promise\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This BuzzMachine post argues that Google 's rush toward ubiquity might backfire -- which we 've all heard before , but it 's particularly well - put in this post .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"heard\", does the state of the participant \"we\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The millions who died in the Iran - Iraq war had nothing to do with Israel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the state of the participant \"millions\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Liquidweb.com Rocks !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Rocks\", does the state of the participant \"Liquidweb.com\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said Mr Dar , 33 , was arrested in Indian - administered Kashmir and belonged to the outlawed Lashkar - e - Toiba militant group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"He\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Once upon a time ( in 2001 , to be specific ) , the Coca - Cola corporation built a bottling plant in a small and remote Indian village in the state of Kerala .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the state of the participant \"plant\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The price of crude oil on the international market hit a record $ 70.85 a barrel due to the vulnerability of oil and gas fields in the Gulf of Mexico .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hit\", does the state of the participant \"$\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bradley 's record of 300 phenophases found that even prior to 1999 , spring was arriving in higher latitudes several weeks earlier than in the earlier years of her data .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arriving\", does the state of the participant \"spring\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Dr. Mann killed our pet\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the state of the participant \"pet\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Rock revolution happened in the Sixties ( 6 , number of the Beast ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"happened\", does the state of the participant \"revolution\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"you play too much cod ;P\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the state of the participant \"you\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"She had to hack her way through the ceiling of her beauty shop as flood waters rose in the city of half a million people - much of which lies below sea level .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rose\", does the state of the participant \"waters\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I asked them to change it but they rudely said that it was okay .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"An incredible number of people in the Arab world believe that September 11 never happened , or was an American provocation or , even better , a Jewish plot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"happened\", does the state of the participant \"September\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I work for a large retail company recently expanding our operations into Canada and had to travel to ensure all of our computer network equipment was installed properly and on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"work\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"( Participants pledged to raise at least $ 100,000 by bundling together cheques of up to $ 1,000 from friends and family .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raise\", does the state of the participant \"$\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A woman walks into an Israeli restaurant in mid-day , eats , observes families with old people and children eating their lunch in the adjacent tables and pays the bill .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eating\", does the state of the participant \"lunch\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We recommend these cabins !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recommend\", does the state of the participant \"cabins\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Most experts believe China intends to develop a small space station of its own over the next several years .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"develop\", does the state of the participant \"station\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Restaurant on top was renovated , food was decent , price was way to high for Duluth for quality , new decor seems tacky\"\nQuestion: In the event \"renovated\", does the state of the participant \"Restaurant\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Allawi 's aged cousin and the man 's wife and daughter - in - law were abducted and guerrillas threaten to behead them if the Fallujah compaign is not stopped .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"behead\", does the state of the participant \"them\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Their screams changed , \" Dr. Fortier said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"changed\", does the state of the participant \"screams\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The other stylists around me kept pressuring me saying he 's so wonderful , you 're going to love your hair .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the state of the participant \"stylists\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Tangipahoa Parish sheriff 's deputy Christopher Blair Labat , 24 , was booked Tuesday on one count of aggravated rape and one count of crime against nature .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the state of the participant \"Labat\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The rapid victory during the first Gulf War cemented this perception .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cemented\", does the state of the participant \"perception\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I used my card to purchase a meal on the menu and the total on my receipt was $ 8.95 but when I went on line to check my transaction it show $ 10.74 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the state of the participant \"card\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"There are only about 850 wolves in the West , but there are an estimated 31,000 mountain lions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the state of the participant \"wolves\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have the opportunity to pick up a super nice 6 year old for free .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"opportunity\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Winter defied his own board and Gov. Gray Davis when he filed a 50 - page request to remove the caps , records and interviews show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remove\", does the state of the participant \"caps\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"James Bateman came the day I called and fixed the problem quickly and efficiently .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the state of the participant \"problem\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"'' It was the first time that Bush totally focused on the Taliban threat rather than Al Qaeda with the Pakistanis , '' says a Western diplomat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"focused\", does the state of the participant \"Bush\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bangs said although the number of elk has not declined very much since the wolves came back , their behavior appears markedly different .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"appears\", does the state of the participant \"behavior\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"One thought is to have just the agenda as a couple topics and then lead in with the first two questions as I 've listed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the state of the participant \"thought\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Sheikh Naji Al - Abbudi , a spokesman for Sistani , affirmed the claims that the Grand Ayatollah is backing the United Iraqi Coalition list .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"backing\", does the state of the participant \"list\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My assistant Joanne Rozycki has cell , car numbers to reach me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the state of the participant \"numbers\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I melt brass and cast it http://www.mikegigi.com/castgobl.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"melt\", does the state of the participant \"brass\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bangs said the agency has established viable wolf packs in the northern Rockies , as required by federal regulations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"established\", does the state of the participant \"packs\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She had to hack her way through the ceiling of her beauty shop as flood waters rose in the city of half a million people - much of which lies below sea level .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rose\", does the state of the participant \"waters\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In Calcutta there is a Foreigner 's reservation office where they speak English very well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"speak\", does the state of the participant \"English\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The Briggs Declaration states that with one exception in 1972 , Wilson did not work \" directly or indirectly \" for the CIA since retiring .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"states\", does the state of the participant \"Declaration\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The main reason I wrote this post is to ask anyone reading this if they know of some way I can help put a stop to this Cat Holocaust .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wrote\", does the state of the participant \"post\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The United States was to cut its level by 7 per cent .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cut\", does the state of the participant \"level\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Phenology studies an organism 's development and life cycle -- the pulse of life .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"studies\", does the state of the participant \"Phenology\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have to mention that i recently separated the father into another cage close to the ' nest cage ' because he and the mother were fighting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"separated\", does the state of the participant \"father\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I asked them to change it but they rudely said that it was okay .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A little birdie told me that you were checking into tickets for Seoul .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"checking\", does the state of the participant \"you\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" The governor believes it was the defining moment , when what was a mounting problem turned into an instant crisis , \" Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"turned\", does the state of the participant \"what\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"'' It was the first time that Bush totally focused on the Taliban threat rather than Al Qaeda with the Pakistanis , '' says a Western diplomat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"focused\", does the state of the participant \"Bush\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Their Club sandwich looks tasty , maybe that 'll change my mind .... and a different server .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the state of the participant \"mind\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Al Qaeda members and sympathizers feel that the FBI 's involvement in countries like Egypt , Saudi Arabia , Pakistan , Indonesia , and the Philippines interferes with the sovereignty of those countries .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interferes\", does the state of the participant \"involvement\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Jewish marriage living to the right of George 's house said that he is an arrogant person who does never return a greeting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"marriage\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In the words of my new accountant , THEY LET ME DOWN !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LET\", does the state of the participant \"ME\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A state Senate committee is set today to start serving 16 subpoenas on electricity producers and officials who manage California 's energy grid to determine whether they acted in concert to manipulate energy prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manipulate\", does the state of the participant \"prices\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They wanted to brainwash them and control them . ''\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brainwash\", does the state of the participant \"them\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Arial photos of the lab were uranium is being enriched , somewhat like those of chemical weapons stockpiles in Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enriched\", does the state of the participant \"uranium\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There is considerable evidence that it is developing both a long - range missile force and a range of weapons of mass destruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"developing\", does the state of the participant \"force\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" He left a message for everyone to see ... maybe to God himself . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the state of the participant \"message\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Seth provides deep tissue massage which has significantly reduced the pain in my neck and shoulders and added flexibility and movement back to the area .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reduced\", does the state of the participant \"pain\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I presume you need the Pakistan base for rescue operations in case anything went wrong .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"presume\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Wolfowitz lied to him and said that there was a 10 to 50 % chance that Iraq was behind them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lied\", does the state of the participant \"Wolfowitz\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My vet told me when a dog is vomiting a lot , it could be a sign of obstruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the state of the participant \"vet\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I think it will help me very much in my role .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The dealer wanted $ 1300 to fix that and another $ 1500 to fix some other things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the state of the participant \"things\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" It was about how he could humiliate her the most , \" prosecutor Dean Mandros said in closing arguments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"Mandros\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Mine learned to \" go to the bathroom \" only in their cages and loved to ride on my shoulder or hang out in my hoodie pouch .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"learned\", does the state of the participant \"Mine\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Huge amounts of money , which could have solved many social problems in this dysfunctional part of the world , are channeled into three concentric spheres supporting death and murder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"solved\", does the state of the participant \"amounts\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It 's become a guardian of morality -- not church morality ; real morality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"become\", does the state of the participant \"It\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The rapid victory during the first Gulf War cemented this perception .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cemented\", does the state of the participant \"perception\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The only problem that I had in 2 years of living there was that the walls are pretty thin , sometimes I could here my neighbors conversations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"here\", does the state of the participant \"conversations\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This year a newspaper claimed two UK firms were involved in a deal in which thousands of guns for Iraqi forces were re-routed to al - Qaeda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"re-routed\", does the state of the participant \"thousands\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In the words of my new accountant , THEY LET ME DOWN !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LET\", does the state of the participant \"ME\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Our new lunar transportation system utilizes a unique architecture that will establish the equivalent of a two - way highway between the Earth and the Moon , \" Kistler told SPACE.com .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"establish\", does the state of the participant \"equivalent\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I hope you do n't change your mind about going to the wedding Sunday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Joe removed a wasp nest for our condominium building and we appreciated the environmentally friendly method and prompt , friendly and informative service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"appreciated\", does the state of the participant \"we\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The Rock revolution happened in the Sixties ( 6 , number of the Beast ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"happened\", does the state of the participant \"revolution\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This defeats the purpose of using a Tradename .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defeats\", does the state of the participant \"purpose\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"President Bush loves him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loves\", does the state of the participant \"him\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I got highlights , haircut , and a blowdry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Dale \" means \" river valley . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"means\", does the state of the participant \"Dale\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This draft reflects the changes we discussed during our call the other day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reflects\", does the state of the participant \"changes\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This action accelerated the utilities ' move toward bankruptcy and forced the governor to move the state into the power - buying business . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accelerated\", does the state of the participant \"action\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They treat there employees with respect and concern and expect that they will extend the same politeness to there customers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extend\", does the state of the participant \"politeness\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"they fixed my garage doors in literally less than an hour .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the state of the participant \"doors\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have to mention that i recently separated the father into another cage close to the ' nest cage ' because he and the mother were fighting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"separated\", does the state of the participant \"father\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"jill allen finishes her cpa today and she and her friends are going to party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finishes\", does the state of the participant \"allen\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In Texas , BP shut its 460,000 barrels per day refinery and Marathon shut its 72,000 bpd plant .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shut\", does the state of the participant \"Marathon\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Israel owes the United States at least this much , in this crisis , to cease militarily unnecessary provocations and establish genuine peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cease\", does the state of the participant \"provocations\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said it was the same tire , and verified this , after checking both the actual tire on my car and my service papers from earlier in the week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"He\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The impacts of climate change on the region and the globe are projected to increase substantially in the years to come . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"projected\", does the state of the participant \"impacts\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We need for interviewers to commit either to the morning ( 9 am - 12 pm ) or afternoon ( 2 pm - 5 pm ) complete session .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commit\", does the state of the participant \"interviewers\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I melt brass and cast it http://www.mikegigi.com/castgobl.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cast\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I asked them to change it but they rudely said that it was okay .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I hope you do n't change your mind about going to the wedding Sunday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a few entities that may need to change groups or be assigned to a group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the state of the participant \"entities\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I was told to take my coffee to go if I wanted to finish it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finish\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There 's plenty of parking , and I 've never had an issue with audience members who wo n't stop talking or answering their cellphones .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stop\", does the state of the participant \"members\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The food tasted like rat feces\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tasted\", does the state of the participant \"food\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In the end Nixon kept his promise for \" . peace with honor .. \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the state of the participant \"Nixon\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I did the same thing that you did for christmas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the state of the participant \"thing\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In other words the table is set .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"set\", does the state of the participant \"table\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I tamed them in 4 days .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tamed\", does the state of the participant \"them\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bradley 's record of 300 phenophases found that even prior to 1999 , spring was arriving in higher latitudes several weeks earlier than in the earlier years of her data .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arriving\", does the state of the participant \"spring\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kill\", does the state of the participant \"eggs\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" The problem is not with the Palestinian resistance groups but with Israel 's scheme to destroy the Palestinians ' infrastructure , \" Habib said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"destroy\", does the state of the participant \"infrastructure\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I prefer to devote most of my remarks to the broader picture of the region and its place in world events .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"devote\", does the state of the participant \"most\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"MFJ Inc transformed our run down back yard into a place of beauty .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transformed\", does the state of the participant \"yard\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"'' It was the first time that Bush totally focused on the Taliban threat rather than Al Qaeda with the Pakistanis , '' says a Western diplomat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"focused\", does the state of the participant \"Bush\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I MAKE MONEY NOT DEAL WITH BROKERS \" Wow , can you believe in today s tough times this dealership would be looking for any way to move vehicles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"MAKE\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"During the session , he demanded to have my physical address , which I 've always kept private as I am enrolled in a witness protection program .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enrolled\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Last week , Federal District Judge Lynn Hughes in Huston , Texas , threw out Wilson 's two - decades old conviction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threw\", does the state of the participant \"Hughes\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Restaurant on top was renovated , food was decent , price was way to high for Duluth for quality , new decor seems tacky\"\nQuestion: In the event \"renovated\", does the state of the participant \"Restaurant\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They kept the name Oracle and created the RDBMS engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"created\", does the state of the participant \"engine\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bradley 's record of 300 phenophases found that even prior to 1999 , spring was arriving in higher latitudes several weeks earlier than in the earlier years of her data .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arriving\", does the state of the participant \"spring\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The dealer wanted $ 1300 to fix that and another $ 1500 to fix some other things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the state of the participant \"things\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He looked like a great guy for your group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"looked\", does the state of the participant \"He\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My assistant Joanne Rozycki has cell , car numbers to reach me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the state of the participant \"numbers\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The US lost yet another helicopter to hostile fire near Habbaniyah in the Sunni heartland , but this time the crew was safe .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the state of the participant \"US\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"All you have to do is become a member and watch your earnings grow !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grow\", does the state of the participant \"earnings\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I use Miracle Cloth , they 're fantastic , just do n't use fabric softener or dryer sheets when cleaning them , it ruins their \" grabbing \" ability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ruins\", does the state of the participant \"ability\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The main reason I wrote this post is to ask anyone reading this if they know of some way I can help put a stop to this Cat Holocaust .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reading\", does the state of the participant \"this\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Both India and Afghanistan deny the claim .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deny\", does the state of the participant \"claim\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I sent a graphic that would have been distorted if printed as it was .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"distorted\", does the state of the participant \"graphic\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I did the same thing that you did for christmas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the state of the participant \"thing\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The rapid victory during the first Gulf War cemented this perception .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cemented\", does the state of the participant \"perception\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"All you can do is take each section ( individual video ) and edit them together on software .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"edit\", does the state of the participant \"them\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Yes , there is a 100 year - old Israeli - Arab conflict , but it is not where the main show is .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the state of the participant \"conflict\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"First room had used tissues next to the bed and I requested it be rectified .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rectified\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"you play too much cod ;P\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the state of the participant \"you\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"By the late 1990s , Iraq had no nuclear or biological weapons program , and had destroyed its chemical weapons stockpiles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"destroyed\", does the state of the participant \"stockpiles\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Texas Education Reform Caucus is made up of business leaders , educators , and elected officials dedicated to finding common sense approaches to improving education in Texas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"improving\", does the state of the participant \"education\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the state of the participant \"laptop\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Attached is the revised draft paper that reflects our conference call with Bob Fagan earlier this week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the state of the participant \"paper\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This draft reflects the changes we discussed during our call the other day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reflects\", does the state of the participant \"changes\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The main reason I wrote this post is to ask anyone reading this if they know of some way I can help put a stop to this Cat Holocaust .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wrote\", does the state of the participant \"post\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The recent elections in Iraq were dominated by an amalgam of religiously fundamentalist Shi'ite organizations , principally the Dawa Party and the Supreme Council for Islamic Revolution in Iraq ( SCIRI ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dominated\", does the state of the participant \"elections\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had this ridiculous celebrity stylist from LA named Derrick .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The missile 's manufacturers state that one or two missiles could cripple a destroyer , and five missiles could sink a 20,000 ton ship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sink\", does the state of the participant \"ship\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He faxed it to you and will have the original Fedexed overnight .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"faxed\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The mass murder happening right now in Sudan , where the Arab Moslem regime is massacring its black Christian citizens , has nothing to do with Israel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"massacring\", does the state of the participant \"citizens\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Mine learned to \" go to the bathroom \" only in their cages and loved to ride on my shoulder or hang out in my hoodie pouch .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"learned\", does the state of the participant \"Mine\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"n3td3v saw this story on BBC News Online and thought you should see it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the state of the participant \"story\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know that with my industry - wide and investment banking contacts that I can help raise capital for the fund .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raise\", does the state of the participant \"capital\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I KNOW YOU HAVE A LOT GOING ON WITH YOU AND THE LITTLE WOMAN .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"KNOW\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I sent a graphic that would have been distorted if printed as it was .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"distorted\", does the state of the participant \"graphic\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have my paralegal gathering the pleadings Enron requested .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"requested\", does the state of the participant \"Enron\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a 9 month old German Shepherd that I raised from a puppy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raised\", does the state of the participant \"Shepherd\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I recommend this company to ANYONE and everyone that needs great work done at a reasonable rate !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recommend\", does the state of the participant \"company\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they do some good waterproof raincoats\"\nQuestion: In the event \"do\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"President Bush pinched a few nerves yesterday with his choice of words :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pinched\", does the state of the participant \"Bush\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He vacated the FWS decision to downgrade the wolf 's status .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"downgrade\", does the state of the participant \"status\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Israel owes the United States at least this much , in this crisis , to cease militarily unnecessary provocations and establish genuine peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cease\", does the state of the participant \"provocations\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The new Centre has 4 studios planned and now boasts the largest single dance floor area in Kingston upon Hull .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the state of the participant \"studios\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I did the same thing that you did for christmas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A girl raises her hand .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raises\", does the state of the participant \"hand\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We need for interviewers to commit either to the morning ( 9 am - 12 pm ) or afternoon ( 2 pm - 5 pm ) complete session .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commit\", does the state of the participant \"interviewers\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I saw lots of videos about this , but actually it did n't help .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the state of the participant \"lots\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Your suggestion to introduce the concept discussed with one of the Lays is welcomed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"introduce\", does the state of the participant \"concept\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i need to now get a job at house of pies b/c that is the only way to pay the bills .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pay\", does the state of the participant \"bills\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" There is always the possibility they could jam us up , make us look like we are not numero uno , \" Pike said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"Pike\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" They ( ISO management ) did what any independent system operator would do . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the state of the participant \"They\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In the Oct. 31 letters , electricity producers told federal officials that if price caps were n't removed it would lead to a collapse of the energy market .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the state of the participant \"caps\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"More people die from AIDS in one day in Africa than all the Russians who died in the hands of Chechnya - based Moslem suicide murderers since that conflict started .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"die\", does the state of the participant \"people\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Nobody thinks that there will be a lot of oil and gas in this part of the world , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"he\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Another worrisome sign is that local Iraqi Sunni fundamentalists opposed to the US presence in Iraq have begun joining Monotheism and Holy War , and wearing its distinctive orange and black insignia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wearing\", does the state of the participant \"insignia\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another worrisome sign is that local Iraqi Sunni fundamentalists opposed to the US presence in Iraq have begun joining Monotheism and Holy War , and wearing its distinctive orange and black insignia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wearing\", does the state of the participant \"insignia\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I did the same thing that you did for christmas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I need something reliable and good looking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the state of the participant \"something\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But there are just so many poses and programs !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the state of the participant \"poses\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The next day i took it to 2 auto shops and they both told me the same thing , engine is junk .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the state of the participant \"i\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The Jewish marriage living to the right of George 's house said that he is an arrogant person who does never return a greeting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"marriage\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Seth provides deep tissue massage which has significantly reduced the pain in my neck and shoulders and added flexibility and movement back to the area .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reduced\", does the state of the participant \"pain\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Dessert was ... hmmm , that 's interesting , I do n't even remember dessert .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remember\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Bangs said the agency has established viable wolf packs in the northern Rockies , as required by federal regulations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"established\", does the state of the participant \"packs\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ordered 1000 postcards , we normally order 5000 or more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rigged\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Your fellow employees asked for everyone from Britney Spears to George Bush .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the state of the participant \"employees\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"New Orleans mayor Ray Nagin said up to 80 % of the city was submerged , in some cases by waters 6 m ( 20 ft ) deep .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"submerged\", does the state of the participant \"%\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Texas Education Reform Caucus is made up of business leaders , educators , and elected officials dedicated to finding common sense approaches to improving education in Texas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"improving\", does the state of the participant \"education\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I expected to pay for this service , but imagine my surprise when I received a bill for MORE than what I paid to have the original return prepared .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the state of the participant \"what\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A woman walks into an Israeli restaurant in mid-day , eats , observes families with old people and children eating their lunch in the adjacent tables and pays the bill .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eating\", does the state of the participant \"lunch\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i need to now get a job at house of pies b/c that is the only way to pay the bills .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pay\", does the state of the participant \"bills\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"YOU GET WHAT YOU PAY FOR !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"PAY\", does the state of the participant \"YOU\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" They ( ISO management ) did what any independent system operator would do . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the state of the participant \"They\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Climate : Humans fuss , animals adjust\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adjust\", does the state of the participant \"animals\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The last wolf was killed in Yellowstone National Park in 1943 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the state of the participant \"wolf\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My car broke down and roadside towed my vehicle to Sussman Kia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broke\", does the state of the participant \"car\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I guess they figured me for an easy mark , and tried to explain that my car would n't pass unless I replaced a hose .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"replaced\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"It put hair on my chest and thanks to the owner s advice I invested vanguard , got myself a woman like Jerry , and became a republican .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"put\", does the state of the participant \"hair\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"n3td3v saw this story on BBC News Online and thought you should see it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the state of the participant \"story\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i satisfy your appetitie for lovin .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"satisfy\", does the state of the participant \"appetitie\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Our new lunar transportation system utilizes a unique architecture that will establish the equivalent of a two - way highway between the Earth and the Moon , \" Kistler told SPACE.com .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"utilizes\", does the state of the participant \"architecture\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We all enjoy buying a snack when visiting a town or attraction while on holiday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoy\", does the state of the participant \"We\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I ordered 1000 postcards , we normally order 5000 or more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I asked them to change it but they rudely said that it was okay .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the state of the participant \"it\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In Ramadi , there was a big demonstration .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"was\", does the state of the participant \"demonstration\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Yazid Sufaat provided Moussaoui with a letter indicating that he was a marketing representative for Infocus Technologies and allegedly provided him $ 35,000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provided\", does the state of the participant \"$\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Briggs Declaration states that with one exception in 1972 , Wilson did not work \" directly or indirectly \" for the CIA since retiring .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"states\", does the state of the participant \"Declaration\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Huge amounts of money , which could have solved many social problems in this dysfunctional part of the world , are channeled into three concentric spheres supporting death and murder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"solved\", does the state of the participant \"amounts\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This year a newspaper claimed two UK firms were involved in a deal in which thousands of guns for Iraqi forces were re-routed to al - Qaeda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"re-routed\", does the state of the participant \"thousands\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Texas Education Reform Caucus is made up of business leaders , educators , and elected officials dedicated to finding common sense approaches to improving education in Texas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"improving\", does the state of the participant \"education\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The prestigious IAEA ( International Atomic Energy Agency ) published an early report on Chernobyl which was based on information from Russian sources and stated that there was no significant health effects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"published\", does the state of the participant \"report\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The recent elections in Iraq were dominated by an amalgam of religiously fundamentalist Shi'ite organizations , principally the Dawa Party and the Supreme Council for Islamic Revolution in Iraq ( SCIRI ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dominated\", does the state of the participant \"elections\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The missile 's manufacturers state that one or two missiles could cripple a destroyer , and five missiles could sink a 20,000 ton ship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cripple\", does the state of the participant \"missiles\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bangs said his agency is still reviewing the decision .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the state of the participant \"Bangs\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I understand how competitive the process has become , but I felt that with my work experiences , recommendations , personality , extracurricular activities , etc. that this would compensate for my disability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"become\", does the state of the participant \"process\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We need to change the lock and place posted signs at the gate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"place\", does the state of the participant \"signs\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Tamils feel that the proposed defense agreement between India and Sri Lanka would encourage Sinhala rulers to prepare for another war abandoning the current peace process\"\nQuestion: In the event \"abandoning\", does the state of the participant \"process\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Paula has an amazing gift for creativity , vision and the ability to combine art to / with commercial purpose .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"combine\", does the state of the participant \"art\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There are several just off their beautiful beach .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the state of the participant \"several\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"That means making yourself known ; that means networking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"means\", does the state of the participant \"That\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The good news is that all of this is temporary , because the evolution of international law has always adapted itself to reality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adapted\", does the state of the participant \"itself\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They wanted to brainwash them and control them . ''\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brainwash\", does the state of the participant \"them\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"You all remember the Iraqi Minister of Information , Mr. Mouhamad Said al - Sahaf and his press conferences when the US forces were already inside Baghdad .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remember\", does the state of the participant \"Minister\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We need to include all outstanding transactions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"include\", does the state of the participant \"transactions\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Across the United States , the northern edge of species ' range is expanding , \" she said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expanding\", does the state of the participant \"edge\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the state of the participant \"they\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In the end Nixon kept his promise for \" . peace with honor .. \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the state of the participant \"Nixon\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"During the session , he demanded to have my physical address , which I 've always kept private as I am enrolled in a witness protection program .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enrolled\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Wolfowitz lied to him and said that there was a 10 to 50 % chance that Iraq was behind them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lied\", does the state of the participant \"Wolfowitz\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"There 's plenty of parking , and I 've never had an issue with audience members who wo n't stop talking or answering their cellphones .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stop\", does the state of the participant \"members\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another worrisome sign is that local Iraqi Sunni fundamentalists opposed to the US presence in Iraq have begun joining Monotheism and Holy War , and wearing its distinctive orange and black insignia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wearing\", does the state of the participant \"insignia\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" Should the Arctic Ocean become ice - free in summer , it is likely that polar bears and some seal species would be driven toward extinction , \" the report concluded .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"driven\", does the state of the participant \"bears\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"MFJ Inc transformed our run down back yard into a place of beauty .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transformed\", does the state of the participant \"yard\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fungus\", does the state of the participant \"eggs\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Our new lunar transportation system utilizes a unique architecture that will establish the equivalent of a two - way highway between the Earth and the Moon , \" Kistler told SPACE.com .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"utilizes\", does the state of the participant \"architecture\" change?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I adopted a 3.5 month old yellow lab last winter from the Dumb Friends League .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adopted\", does the state of the participant \"I\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"On August 21st , 2009 I ordered furniture from Hickory Furniture Mart and contracted for HDS to deliver it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the state of the participant \"furniture\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Liquidweb.com Rocks !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Rocks\", does the state of the participant \"Liquidweb.com\" change?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Every student of political science debates how you prevent an anti-democratic force from winning a democratic election and abolishing democracy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"winning\", does the state of the participant \"election\" change?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}]